immediateedge.com 2016-02-01

# The Immediate Edge

We are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We provide certain services and opportunities for users of our web site and members of our organization. In order to provide these services, we require that you submit some personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. 

#### Information Gathered

When you become a member of our website to access content or download materials from our site, or by direct email signup, purchasing one of our products, providing feedback, or contacting us in any way, We are collecting information from you. This information is necessary to communicate with you, to fulfil your requests regarding information and products, to provide you with the products you have purchased, and to contact you about your products or other Raine Ventures LLC products. 

#### Emailing You

We will email you from time to time with product updates, information we think you might find useful, and offers to other products or services. You can opt-out this correspondence at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link which is at the bottom of all our emails to you. 

#### Information Sharing

We will not sell, rent, or share your personally identifiable information with others, unless we have your permission or are required to do so by law. We will not share aggregate data with our sponsors, members or other parties. 

#### Use Of Contractors

We may retain the service of outside contractors to perform services on our behalf (for example, to help provide technical support services or deliver new products or services). At times, we must disclose relevant personally identifiable information about you to our contractors so they may provide these specific services for us. We require our contractors to keep this information confidential and to only use the information on our behalf. 

#### Cookies

We use cookies and sessions on our site to manage your log in to our network of sites and for other site management purposes. Cookies are also used to manage our advertising system but you are not personally identifiable by these. 

#### Links To Third Party Websites

Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy and information collection practices. 

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may amend this policy occasionally. It is your responsibility to check this page for any notices of change. 

By signing up and joining as a member of The Immediate Edge you are agreeing this Privacy Policy, and also to the Terms & Conditions, Earnings Disclaimer, and Payments Policy that you should have also read.
